https://gointuition.com/privacy-policy/

My AccountCheckoutCartHomeAboutAnne SalisburyGreg MeyerhoffAll That Is ChannelingsFAQs & Definitions of IntuitionMedia KitResources & LinksPoliciesSessionsSession FormGreat LifeBusiness SeminarsTalksEventsPhotos of Experts & EventsShopSessionsGreat Life EmpowermentEventsBooksIntuitive Skills CoursesMake a PaymentTestimonialsBlogFreeContactWho we areThe Privacy Policy will become effective on May 25th, 2018.At Go Intuition we care about your privacy and believe in transparency. That’s why we are committed to being upfront about our privacy practices. We only collect personal information necessary to deliver our services and we handle it carefully and sensibly.Anne Salisbury, PhD, MBA, is an intuitive who helps people find answers to those important uestions in life.Greg Meyerhoff, CPC, is an intuitive coach who helps people break through energy blocks to experience success with ease.Anne Salisbury, PhD, CCHt and Greg Meyerhoff, CCHt, Directors Go Intuition, Inc. P. O. Box 18409, Golden, Colorado 80402 USA303-278-9585Contact UsWhat personal data we collect and why we collect itContact FormWe store Contact Form Submissions in case an email fails to get through to us: Name, Email, Phone, MessageNewsletterWe use Constant Contact to store your newsletter signup information. Constant Contact stores your email and any other information you provide when you sign up for the newsletter.Site ProtectData Used: In order to check login activity and potentially block fraudulent attempts, the following information is used: attempting user’s IP address, attempting user’s email address/username (i.e. according to the value they were attempting to use during the login process), and all IP-related HTTP headers attached to the attempting user.Activity Tracked: Failed login attempts (these include IP address and user agent).Data Synced: Failed login attempts, which contain the user’s IP address, attempted username or email address, and user agent information.WooCommerce Online Shopping Cart PluginWhile you visit our site, we’ll track:Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewedLocation, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shippingShipping address: we’ll ask you to enter this so we can estimate shipping before you place an order, and send you the order.We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.When you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We’ll use this information for the following purposes:Send you information about your account and orderRespond to your requests, including refunds and complaintsProcess payments and prevent fraudSet up your account for our storeComply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxesImprove our store offeringIf you create an account, we will store your name, address, email and phone number, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.We generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. For example, we will store order information for 8 years for tax and accounting purposes. This includes your name, email address and billing and shipping addresses.We will also store comments or reviews, if you choose to leave them.PaymentsWe use Stripe and Paypal to process credit card payments. All credit card data is stored at Stripeor Paypal.Google AnalyticsData Used: Please refer to the appropriate Google Analytics documentation for the specific type of data it collects. For sites running WooCommerce, purchase events will send Google Analytics the following information: order number, product id and name, product category, total cost, and quantity of items purchased. Google Analytics does offer IP anonymization, which can be enabled by the site owner.Activity Tracked: This feature sends page view events (and potentially video play events) over to Google Analytics for consumption. For sites running WooCommerce-powered stores, some additional events are also sent to Google Analytics.WordPress.com StatsData Used: IP address, WordPress.com user ID (if logged in), WordPress.com username (if logged in), user agent, visiting URL, referring URL, timestamp of event, browser language, country code. Important: The site owner does not have access to any of this information via this feature. For example, a site owner can see that a specific post has 285 views, but he/she cannot see which specific users/accounts viewed that post. Stats logs — containing visitor IP addresses and WordPress.com usernames (if available) — are retained by Automattic for 28 days and are used for the sole purpose of powering this feature.Activity Tracked: Post and page views, video plays (if videos are hosted by WordPress.com), outbound link clicks, referring URLs and search engine terms, and country. When this module is enabled, Jetpack also tracks performance on each page load that includes the Javascript file used for tracking stats. This is exclusively for aggregate performance tracking across Jetpack sites in order to make sure that our plugin and code is not causing performance issues. This includes the tracking of page load times and resource loading duration (image files, Javascript files, CSS files, etc.). The site owner has the ability to force this feature to honor DNT settings of visitors. By default, DNT is currently not honored.Who we share your data withWe do not share our data with anyone.CookiesWe use Cookies to collect some of the information set out in this Policy. A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in your web browser on your computer, mobile or other handheld device, while you are browsing a website.Our Site uses cookies to identify you. Cookies can store your account identifier, ordering status, personalisation or website tracking. They can also be used for technical purposes such as keeping track of your current shopping session and enabling you to proceed to checkout and pay for your according order or to save information which has already been entered so we can offer improved and more personalised services, products and other relevant communication tailored to you.You can also modify your Cookie preferences straight from your browser. Please note that if you disable all of our cookies or cookies in general in your browser settings, you may find that certain sections or features of our Site will not work, because your browser may prevent us from setting Site functionally required cookies.How Long We Retain Your DataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. Contact Us if you want a copy of your data or if you want your data removed.How we protect your dataWe use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encrypt the information you enter on our Site in order to protect its security during transmission to and from our Site. When storing information, we protect its security by encryption. When we process credit card information and payments, the credit card is subject strong security measures provided by Stripe and Paypal.Retention periodsInformation collected on our website will only be retained for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. In general, we will automatically delete your User Area account information 2 years after you no longer have any active services with us. Since we offer a service for customers worldwide and we need to comply with regulations across the globe in regard to retention of personal information related to contractual agreements, provision of services, financial, billing, invoicing operations and tax calculations, a versioned copy of your contact, payment and billing personal data associated with your past invoices is stored for a period of 7 years and 10 years for payroll records after deactivating an account . Your personal data is deleted automatically by our systems in accordance with these retention periods.Your RightsBy visiting the My Account page, you can your email or billing and shipping addresses.  If you need further assistance, you can contact us for help with any of the following:confirm whether or not personal data about you is being processedprovide you with further details about how we process your personal dataprovide you with a copy of any data which we hold about yourequest to update or delete personal data which we hold about youPlease note that we may ask you to provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity before responding.What data breach procedures we have in placeIf there is a data breach on our website, we will contact all registered users within 72 hours of when we determine there was a breach. CartReceive Go Intuition eNews!Sign-up to receive your "Go Intuition" news with fascinating articles each month. Privacy Policy
Product CategoriesAudios on Intuition - Out of stock (2)Books on Intuition (4)Courses on Intuition Online (0)Great Life Empowerment (5)Intuition Events (5)Sessions: Personal, Business (17)Uncategorized (2)Blog CategoriesBlog (65)Book Reviews & Excepts (8)Business Consulting (4)Connect with Loved Ones on the Other Side (2)Conversations with All That Is Channelings (5)Develop Your Intuition (12)Downloads (5)Feng Shui & Energy Clearing (2)Ghost Clearing (2)Human-Animal Communication: Pet Psychic Readings (8)Newsletters (40)Pioneers in Intuition Interviews (17)Phone: 303-278-9585 - Fax: 303-474-3071 - Email: info@GoIntuition.com Anne Salisbury, PhD & Greg Meyerhoff, CPC, Co-Directors, Go Intuition, Inc, P. O. Box 18409, Golden, Colorado 80402 USA Receive phone sessions worldwide. Our Colorado offices serve Denver, Boulder, Colorado Springs, Summit County, Vail, Breckenridge, Keystone, Copper Mountain.
Privacy & Cookies: This site uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you agree to their use.
To find out more, including how to control cookies, see here:
Cookie Policy
